const ArrayQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which method is used to add an element at the end of an array?",
        options: ["push()", "pop()", "shift()", "unshift()"],
        correctAnswer: "push()"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which method removes the last element from an array?",
        options: ["shift()", "unshift()", "pop()", "slice()"],
        correctAnswer: "pop()"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which method adds one or more elements to the beginning of an array?",
        options: ["push()", "unshift()", "shift()", "concat()"],
        correctAnswer: "unshift()"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which method removes the first element from an array?",
        options: ["pop()", "shift()", "slice()", "splice()"],
        correctAnswer: "shift()"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which method returns a new array without modifying the original array?",
        options: ["splice()", "push()", "slice()", "pop()"],
        correctAnswer: "slice()"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which method is used to merge two or more arrays?",
        options: ["join()", "concat()", "splice()", "map()"],
        correctAnswer: "concat()"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which property is used to find the number of elements in an array?",
        options: ["size", "count", "length", "index"],
        correctAnswer: "length"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which method converts an array into a string?",
        options: ["map()", "join()", "toString()", "Both join() and toString()"],
        correctAnswer: "Both join() and toString()"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which method executes a function for each array element?",
        options: ["filter()", "map()", "forEach()", "reduce()"],
        correctAnswer: "forEach()"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which method creates a new array with elements that pass a condition?",
        options: ["map()", "filter()", "reduce()", "forEach()"],
        correctAnswer: "filter()"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Which method returns the first element that matches a condition?",
        options: ["filter()", "find()", "map()", "some()"],
        correctAnswer: "find()"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "Which method checks if at least one element satisfies a condition?",
        options: ["every()", "some()", "includes()", "find()"],
        correctAnswer: "some()"
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "Which method checks whether an array contains a specific value?",
        options: ["find()", "some()", "includes()", "indexOf()"],
        correctAnswer: "includes()"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Which method reduces an array to a single value?",
        options: ["map()", "filter()", "reduce()", "forEach()"],
        correctAnswer: "reduce()"
    }
];

export default ArrayQuestions;
